<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<book xml:id="evergreen" xmlns="http://docbook.org/ns/docbook"
      xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" version="5.0" xml:lang="EN"
      xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/2001/xlink">
      <info>
            <title>Evergreen 2.1 Documentation</title>
 		<subtitle>Draft Version</subtitle>
		<corpauthor>Documentation Interest Group</corpauthor>
	         <mediaobject>
			<imageobject>
			<imagedata scalefit="0" fileref="../media/main_logo.jpg"/>
		</imageobject>
		</mediaobject>

		<copyright>
                  <year>2011</year>
                  <holder><link linkend="attributions">Members of the Evergreen Project</link></holder>
		<inlinemediaobject>                   
                </inlinemediaobject>    
            </copyright>
                 <legalnotice>
                  <para><link xlink:title="Creative Commons license"
                              xlink:href="http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/3.0/">  
				 <inlinemediaobject>
                                    <imageobject>
                                          <imagedata scalefit="0"
                                                fileref="http://i.creativecommons.org/l/by-sa/3.0/80x15.png"
                                          />
                                    </imageobject>
                              </inlinemediaobject>    
                  </link></para>
                    <para>This document was updated <?dbtimestamp format="Y-m-d"?>.</para>    
               </legalnotice>
	</info>
	<part xml:id="intro">
            	<info>
                	<title>Introduction</title>
           	</info>	
		<partintro xml:id="intro_intro">
    			<para>The book you’re holding in your hands or viewing on a screen is The Book of Evergreen, the official guide to the 2.x version of the Evergreen open 
			source library automation software.  This guide was produced by the Evergreen Documentation Interest Group (DIG), consisting of numerous volunteers from many 
			different organizations.  The DIG has drawn together, edited, and supplemented pre-existing documentation contributed by libraries and consortia running 
			Evergreen that were kind enough to release their documentation into the creative commons.  For a full list of authors and contributing organizations, 
			see <xref linkend="about_this_documentation"></xref>.  Just like the software it describes, this guide is a work in progress, continually revised to meet 
			the needs of its users, so if you find errors or omissions, please let us know, by contacting the DIG facilitators at 
			<link mailto="docs@evergreen-ils.org">docs@evergreen-ils.org</link>.</para>
    			<para>This guide to Evergreen is intended to meet the needs of front-line library staff, catalogers, library administrators, system administrators, and 
			software developers.  It is organized into Parts, Chapters, and Sections addressing key aspects of the software, beginning with the topics of broadest 
			interest to the largest groups of users and progressing to some of the more specialized and technical topics of interest to smaller numbers of users.</para>
    			<para>Copies of this guide can be accessed in PDF and HTML formats from the Documentation section of 
			<link href="http://evergreen-ils.org/">http://evergreen-ils.org/</link> and are included in DocBook XML format along with the Evergreen 
			source code, available for download from the same Web site.</para>
		</partintro>
		<xi:include href="intro/about_evergreen.xml"/>
		<xi:include href="intro/release_notes.xml"/>
 	</part>
	<part xml:id="opac">
		<info>
			<title>Public Access Catalog</title>
		</info>
		<partintro xml:id="opac_intro">
			<para>This part of the documentation explains how to use the Evergreen public OPAC. It covers the basic catalog and more advanced search topics. It also 
			describes the <quote>My Account</quote> tools users have to find information and manage their personal library accounts through the OPAC. This section 
			could be used by staff and patrons but would be more useful for staff as a generic reference when developing custom guides and tutorials for their users.</para>
		</partintro>	
	</part>
	<part xml:id="core_tasks">
		<info>
			<title>Core Staff Tasks</title>
		</info>
		<partintro xml:id="stafftasks_intro">
			<para>This part of the documentation covers a broad range of the common tasks carried out by your library and includes tasks performed by circulation 
			staff and catalogers among others. Some of these procedures should only be performed by Local System Administrators, but most of these sections will give 
			all staff a better understanding of the Evergreen system and its features.</para>
		</partintro>
	
	<!--	<xi:include href="stafftasks/booking.xml"/>
		<xi:include href="stafftasks/acquisitions.xml"/>
		<xi:include href="stafftasks/serials-gpls.xml"/>
		<xi:include href="stafftasks/alternate_serial_control.xml"/>-->
		<xi:include href="stafftasks/cataloging.xml"/>
 	</part>
	<part xml:id="admin">
		<info>
			<title>Administration</title>
		</info>
		<partintro  xml:id="admin_intro">
			<para>This part of the documentation is intended for Evergreen administrators and requires root access to your <application>Evergreen</application> server(s) 
			and administrator access to the <application>Evergreen</application> 
			staff client. It deals with maintaining servers, installation, upgrading, and configuring both system wide and local library settings. 
			Some sections require understanding of <systemitem class="osname">Linux</systemitem> system administration while others require an understanding of your 
			system hierarchy of locations and users. Many procedures explained in the following chapters are accomplished with 
			<systemitem class="osname">Linux</systemitem> commands<indexterm><primary>Linux</primary><secondary>commands</secondary></indexterm> run from the 
			terminal without a Graphical User Interface (GUI).</para>
			<para>In order to accomplish some of the tasks, prerequisite knowledge or experience will be required and you may need to consult system administration 
			documentation for your specific <systemitem class="osname">Linux</systemitem> distribution if you have limited 
			<systemitem class="osname">Linux</systemitem> system experience. A vast ammount of free resources can be found on the on the web for various experinece 
			levels. You might also consider consulting <link xlink:href="http://www.postgresql.org/docs/">
			<application>PostgreSQL</application></link><indexterm><primary>databases</primary><secondary>PostgreSQL</secondary></indexterm> and 
			<link xlink:href="http://httpd.apache.org/docs/"><application>Apache</application></link><indexterm><primary>Apache</primary></indexterm> documentation 
			for a greater understanding of the software stack on which <application>Evergreen</application> is built.</para>
		</partintro>
		<xi:include href="admin/server_install.xml"/>
		<xi:include href="admin/upgrading.xml"/>
		<!--<xi:include href="admin/sip.xml"/>
		<xi:include href="admin/z3950.xml"/>
		<xi:include href="admin/troubleshooting.xml"/>		
		<xi:include href="admin/actiontriggers.xml"/>
		<xi:include href="admin/admin-booking.xml"/>
		<xi:include href="admin/acquisitions_admin_functions.xml"/>
		<xi:include href="admin/localization.xml"/>-->
		
	</part>
	<part xml:id="reports">
		<info>
			<title>Reports</title>
		</info>
		<partintro  xml:id="report_intro">
			<para>Reports are a powerful tool in Evergreen and can be used for statistical comparisons or collection maintenance. The following part covers everything 
			dealing with reports from starting the reporter daemon to viewing reports your library has created. The range of topics in this part is quite broad and 
			different chapters will be useful to different roles in an Evergreen library system.</para>
		</partintro>
		<xi:include href="reports/report-startingreporter.xml"/>
		<xi:include href="reports/report-folder.xml"/>
		<xi:include href="reports/report-create-template.xml"/>
		<xi:include href="reports/report-generate-report.xml"/>
 		<xi:include href="reports/report-view-output.xml"/>
 		<xi:include href="reports/report-shared-template.xml"/>		
 		<xi:include href="reports/report-add-data-source.xml"/>
		<xi:include href="reports/report-recurring-report.xml"/>
 		<xi:include href="reports/report-template-terminology.xml"/>
 		<xi:include href="reports/report-exporting-report-templates-using-phppgadmin.xml"/>
	</part>

	<part xml:id="software_integration">
		<info>
			<title>Third Party System Integration</title>
		</info>
	</part>
	<part xml:id="Development">
		<info>
			<title>Development</title>
		</info>
	<!--	<xi:include href="development/development_intro.xml"/>
		<xi:include href="development/directoriesandFiles.xml"/>	
		<xi:include href="development/customizingstaffclient.xml"/>
		<xi:include href="development/customize_opac.xml"/>
		<xi:include href="development/OpenSRF_intro.xml"/>
		<xi:include href="development/datamodelsandaccess.xml"/>
		<xi:include href="development/introduction_to_sql.xml"/>
		<xi:include href="development/json.xml"/>	
		<xi:include href="development/supercat.xml"/>
-->
	</part>
	<part xml:id="Appendices">
		<info>
			<title>Appendices</title>
		</info>
		<xi:include href="appendices/permissions.xml"/>
		<xi:include href="appendices/schema.xml"/>
		<xi:include href="appendices/about_this_documentation.xml"/>
		<xi:include href="appendices/more_info.xml"/>
		<xi:include href="appendices/glossary.xml"/>
	<!--	<xi:include href="appendices/bookindex.xml"/>-->
	</part>
</book>
